https://www.avantiengineering.com/privacy

(630) 260-1333
Privacy Policy
Avanti Engineering collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Avanti Engineering also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Avanti Engineering. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Avanti Engineering for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Avanti Engineering Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Avanti Engineering public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Avanti Engineering does not read any of your private online communications.
Avanti Engineering encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Avanti Engineering so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Avanti Engineering is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Avanti Engineering and Avanti Engineering family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Avanti Engineering collects and uses your personal information to operate the Avanti Engineering Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Avanti Engineering also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Avanti Engineering and its affiliates. Avanti Engineering may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Avanti Engineering does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Avanti Engineering may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Avanti Engineering may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Avanti Engineering, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Avanti Engineering does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Avanti Engineering keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Avanti Engineering, in order to determine what Avanti Engineering services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Avanti Engineering to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Avanti Engineering Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Avanti Engineering or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Avanti Engineering; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Avanti Engineering, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Avanti Engineering Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Avanti Engineering pages, or register with Avanti Engineering site or services, a cookie helps Avanti Engineering to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Avanti Engineering Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Avanti Engineering features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Avanti Engineering services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Avanti Engineering secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Avanti Engineering secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Avanti Engineering will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Avanti Engineering encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Avanti Engineering is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Avanti Engineering welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Avanti Engineering has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Avanti Engineering at info@avantiengineering.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Ask a Question!
First Name *Email Address *Phone NumberMessage0 / 180Send Message
Avanti Engineering, Inc. 200 West Lake Drive Glendale Hts, Illinois 60139 Phone: (630) 260-1333 Fax: (630) 260-1762
Looking for a screw machine products?
we have you covered!
CONTACT US
We are proud members of
AVANTI ENGINEERING, INC.
200 W. Lake Dr, Glendale Heights, IL 60139
(630) 260-1333
Privacy Policy  |  Terms of Use
